[Music]
[Applause]
Now my heart it beats for you, my Lord.
[Music]
4 years later.
John,
Yeah,
I was offered the job at Water Steps
Designs.
This is good news.
I know. Mom, please eat.
Who are you? What are you doing in my house?
I'm so proud of you.
I know. It's a great opportunity for me.
Wt,
What is that woman doing in our house?
I can't believe I got the job.
before all the young people who
they applied.
Loretta, Loretta,
I'm John, your son-in-law. Okay,
just eat your peas.
I'm not surprised.
Wt, what are you talking about?
It will be good for you to get away from your
mother.
Mother,
Alright.
This chicken is burnt.
I just want to go home.
Are you home, Mom? My house is bigger
beautiful than this place.
And when do you start?
Next week.
No
is.
Hello, honey. Any news?
Hello, Mom.
Yes, it's Raven. She's fine. She can wait.
Can you hear me?
Yes, I'm listening. What happened?
I have something to say.
Mom, I'm on speakerphone.
Yes, he's listening to you. Put me on
to the voice. I listen.
I got engaged.
Wait, what?
Engaged. Raven is engaged.
I can't hear them.
Oh, your sister got engaged.
Do you hear mom?
Yes, listen. He's talking to Ravin.
It's official.
They terminated my contract. I will not play again.
new.
Ah, B, I'm so sorry.
Did you hear me? Hello.
Is it over?
No, it's not over. I'm getting married.
Yes, right? Yes, of course. Who are you with?
will you get married? Did you know something? I'll go home.
Who
are you?
A test of faith. Two. Return home.
[Music]
I managed to calm her down.
Thanks love.
What's that?
I started this when Raven was 5.
Our little girl is getting married.
I know. I can't believe it. And I still don't
we meet the groom.
Ivo, no, I can't believe it. What are we going to do?
do?
What are the odds that
this happen at the same time? I've been waiting
planning this since Ravy was born.
Plan.
Yeah.
Your mother needs you full time.
and you just got your job
dreams.
I can plan Ravin's wedding and take care of
from my mother.
You should hire a nurse.
full-time or part-time.
We've talked about it a thousand times. No
I'll let a stranger take care of my mother.
We will hire a wedding planner. No
I'll let a stranger organize the wedding
of my daughter.
Honey, if you try to do everything, you
you will lose everything.
I won't miss a single moment.
Alexa, I think you can't do everything and
live in the moment. You must choose something.
Yes, Thursday at 9 a.m.
1 2 4.
My plane arrives at 2:30. See you at
the afternoon.
Okay, sorry. Could you repeat the
address?
1 3 with Alberto,
me atoré.
Very well. Ready. Thank you very much.
See you later. Goodbye.
[Music]
Mom. Mom, stay still.
You don't use any milk makeup.
Mom, now
you look tired.
You need to rest.
Oh, it's too tight. You're tying it.
bad. It must be
the left over the right.
Left.
Anyway. Why are you putting me in trouble?
shoes?
Oh, I'm going to sleep.
It's time to sleep.
It's early, Mom. You just
wake up and let's go down to have breakfast.
I don't want to put on my shoes.
Mom, are you okay?
Grandma, why are you hitting my mom? Ah,
my favorite star soccer player.
How is my favorite grandmother?
Better
that was fast.
There is no need to prolong it.
inevitable. Grandma is getting worse.
What do you think if we all go down to
have breakfast? Uh,
I'm sorry, son. I didn't catch your name,
grandmother.
Oh,
God.
[Music]
Here, Mom.
You like this.
[Music]
Thanks, Mom.
We will have a second opinion.
That was the third.
There's nothing they can do. It's a
made.
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
From here, the market.
I didn't give up.
I got kicked off the team. Do you think it was my
decision?
Mother,
what am I going to do now?
Hello.
Look, it's not beautiful.
Wow, that's beautiful. And who gave it to you?
I was thinking we could get married
in the garden under the arch where you
They got married. Wouldn't that be special? It still is.
have.
Yes, I think so. I'll ask your dad.
Hey, there is no greeting for your
brother.
Raven, who?
Mira,
look at this.
I know, I'm so sorry. I swear I
it hurt when you got hurt.
Raven, really? Who are you going to marry?
Oh,
you didn't tell him.
You know. I don't know how to say this.
Wait until you find out who it is.
Es Nathan Adams.
Only Nathan Adams happened.
Yes, my best friend from high school.
Do you remember?
Jessie's son, Nathan.
Oh, wow.
Look who I found walking in the
street.
What did I miss?
Look, Dad, I'm engaged.
[Music]
Hi, I'm Brent. My partner interviewed you.
Nice to meet you.
Things have changed a lot. Everyone
sit together.
Creativity is fueled by
shared energy. We donate 10% of
our profits to provide water
cleans the planet.
I want to see how you will contribute to that.
Thank you and thank you for giving it to us.
opportunity to a mature woman.
I'm sorry.
Oh, don't apologize. You're not answering.
Yeah.
We deduct each call from your payment.
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh,
It was a joke.
I'll show you your desk.
It's there.
You will work here.
Can I see your designs?
Yeah.
Ah, everything is digital. Here you have them in
USB.
Ah, I showed this sketchbook in
my interview.
Yes, we loved them. Do you think you could?
send them all to lunch?
Uh, yeah.
Hey, where is my computer?
Everyone brings their own.
[Music]
Check out my page for wedding ideas.
My daughter will marry my ex's son
best friend and I can't imagine why not
They told me because I already knew him.
They hid something they didn't want to tell me
and my son lost his career. My mother
keeps running away. My daughter will get married and
I literally just started work
of my dreams.
It's too much.
And I must have a relationship with that woman.
Oh. And all John says is live the
moment.
Sometimes husbands can be very
good at minimizing, even if they don't realize it
account. I'm sure it wasn't your
intention.
Oh, whoever invented that one.
expression. He lived alone in the middle of the
nothing without husbands or children, a job or
a father to whom
or a grocery list.
Yes. He could give me back the phone.
to search for the expression live the
moment.
No, no, cell phones in the basket. But no
It was God who invented that thing about living the
moment. It is not a passage from Jesus.
You know what? Let's do it the right way.
traditional. The Bible is better than
Google, right?
I will do it.
God is the author of time.
Mm. Yes, because he goes further.
And how do we apply it to the present?
It gives us the opportunity to ask
aid.
Can you hire help?
Maybe it's time to think about some
nursing options.
No. And if something happens to him, I promised myself that
I would never put her in a nursing home again.
after I missed the death of my
father.
Well, Philippians 4:19 says, "And my God
will provide for all your needs according to
to his riches in glory in Christ
Jesus. If I had riches in glory,
I would have a maid, a chef, a
gardener, a personal chauffeur, a nanny
and a personal assistant.
They are the riches in the glory of God.
Well, I should share them.
Yes, it does. In fact, in the study of
This week, ask yourself, what am I doing?
doing here?
God wants to give us much more than just
our physical needs. He wants us to
let us know that he sees us from right where he is
we are.
He loves us very much
and just wants to fill our hearts.
When we read Elijah, he was in the
mountain of the Lord with the promise that
God would come.
There was a big wind, but God did not
was in the wind. There was fire, but
God was not in the fire. There was even
an earthquake, but God was not in it
earthquake.
God was in a gentle whisper.
Elijah asked him,
"What are you doing here?
[Music]
Wait, there are instructions. It says that
Let's color our tree according to the
station we are in. It is
September, so it's autumn.
Okay. Yes, that's true, but it's
refers to the station of life in which
that we are.
And spring is the time of
learning, opportunities and
reflection. Summer is the time of
rewards, of celebration and
satisfaction, but that is the time of
celebrate because everything is flourishing. In the case
Autumn is the time of change,
to recognize mistakes,
even sometimes the end of a dream.
Winter is the time of hibernation or
of death,
but this time allows us
calm down
and reflect on what we have been through and
also prepare for the next one
season.
What if I don't know what station I'm in?
Calm down,
we're here to find out.
Yes, maybe I could hire someone
to do this activity for me.
That's not living in the moment. Alexa,
[Music]
I love autumn. I automatically used
orange and brown and then
I realized that I am in a
changing station. I don't know what will happen,
but I know that the leaves fall from my tree and
new buds are about to emerge.
Anyone else?
Well, my tree needs no explanation.
[Laughs]
My life is full of activities, life,
everything is blooming, literally
I am blooming.
It's true,
Girls, why don't we use this week
to reflect on our trees
and we wonder what I'm doing
here?
Emily, could you finish with a
prayer?
Of course, God, give us serenity
to accept the things we cannot
change, the courage to change those things
yes and intelligence to
differentiate them. Thank you, Lord. Amen.
Amen.
Have a good week. Thanks for
sharing so much today.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Don't forget what I told you.
No,
Alexa,
Can we talk for a second? Yes,
It is a great privilege to take care of your mother.
Mm.
Not everyone does.
It was very tiring to take care of my grandmother.
before he died. And
This is a center I went to.
It is a wonderful place.
Play lots of games. My grandmother loves it.
loved it. Only when I needed some time
free.
When was the last time you had a
free day?
It's been a while.
Do you want to know my secret for
adapt?
Which?
I don't do it.
Please give yourself a day off.
Will you think about it?
I'll think about it. I love you. Me too.
Goodbye. Goodbye.
[Music]
of the cocks.
[Applause]
[Music]
I'll tell you something, coach. I left the
high school aside when we won the
championship.
You were always good at the game,
but you played with your heart.
And that's something you can't teach.
Although I must say it was a lot of fun.
watching you play on TV. You made me
feel proud.
And look at me now.
I'm broke.
You're not broke. Unless you
rows.
Have you thought about my offer?
What do you see out there? Tell me what you see.
I can only see the past.
It could be your future.
I didn't even go to high school.
These guys have a lot of potential.
We could make the winners together. You
and I would make a great team.
No offense, Coach,
but it is a little discouraging that after
from playing you will be expelled from the team.
Yes, I understand. It's a big change,
but I realized that sometimes in the
life the little unforeseen events are the
that take us on great adventures.
Training teenagers doesn't sound good
exactly to an adventure. You
you would be surprised
because you will see B, at the end of your life
[Music]
It's not success that matters,
but the people around you.
Anyway, consider my offer.
[Music]
I didn't even have time to go
shopping,
Honey, you have a lot of clothes.
Yes, but it's Ravy's commitment.
I need a dress.
It was anticipated.
Yes. And why do I feel completely
excluded from everything? Huh,
I think it was considered that Paul and
Jessie will organize it,
but I want to be able to plan these things.
I wore this to the last party of the
enterprise.
Ah, I don't know. Hey, you look beautiful in it.
whatever you use.
I can't let Jessie look better
that I am. I am the mother of the bride.
This is not a competition.
Yes, yes it is. And I don't want Jessie
identify.
Listen, it will be our family. Could you
leave the past behind to enjoy
this?
I would have enjoyed it if I had been
invited to help at the party
my daughter's commitment.
Okay. I'll help your mom get ready and
you can finish fixing.
whatever you're talking about.
[Music]
Alexa,
Jessie. Oh, so nice to have you here.
Loreta, you look radiant this afternoon.
I'm so sorry. I heard you're
Okay.
Yeah,
let's go for punch.
Where's the cake? Stay.
Alexa,
wait until you see how beautiful everything turned out.
You'll love it.
It's not exciting.
Our children are getting married.
Yes, what a great surprise.
Oh, yes. Nathan's proposal was
beautiful.
I recorded everything. Revin showed it to you.
Were you there? Okay, I can.
send you the video. Clara,
She is Clara Conver. She must be the one
mother of the bride. Raven looks just like you.
We love Raven. Did you notice?
that we incorporate your favorite colors
in the set?
Did you record when they got engaged?
Yes. Did you know that Paul and I moved
near Nathan so we don't miss anything?
I knew they moved, Jessie, but no
I knew that too.
And look what? Now we're moving to a
beautiful house where Nathan will make his
service.
What? I love your daughter. It would be great.
fun to work with her again
to plan the wedding. We believe that this
It would be the perfect place for the
reception.
I don't think so.
Kevin told me everything that is
happening with your mother. I can't
imagine the stress you are going through,
but you won't have to worry about anything
because Clara and I will plan the whole thing
wedding and you'll just have to sit and
enjoy it.
What? I don't think so.
I have searched for the trendy colors and
wedding themes and we want to find
the perfect hashtag for guests and
easily find all the photos you
took from the big day.
Who is she?
I'm Senator Anderson Vino. Come, I'll tell you.
I will introduce. Hello, Senator. Many
Thank you for coming to the party.
It's a pleasure. Thank you very much.
Congratulations. Thank you.
I know I don't need to ask, but
would you be my godfather?
It will be an honor.
Philippians 4:13. He truly helped me in
difficult times.
The first time I enlisted this to me
helped.
I think we both share something now.
Thank you.
Good afternoon everyone.
We really want to thank you all.
for joining us to celebrate this blessed
engagement party.
My wife Jessie and I are happy to
introduce you to our son Nathan Adams
and his lovely fiancée Ravin
Taylor.
[Applause]
Hey, it reminds me of the evil stepmother from
Ashy.
Who?
She.
Oh, no way. Hey, it must be over.
this.
Try to convince her. After she
marry your son, they will force you to do it
the maid of her house and those two
women over there, do you see them? They will be
her evil stepsisters.
Okay, I understand.
In a fantasy world, but in the
actually she was your best friend.
A long time ago.
It's a phrase.
How clever.
How did your parents take this?
I should have told you before.
Why did you wait so long?
It was never a good time. You know that their
expectations are very high.
Hey, it's not about you, it's about your mother.
she
You tell me to calm down. You know that
I hate it when you tell me to calm down. I don't
I like that you tell me to calm down. What?
Mom, please. Oh.
Oh, this pastry is delicious.
It's strong.
Jessie,
where did you get it?
Please people want some
Don't do that, Grandma, please. It's just that
You should fix your hair. No,
it just can't be.
I want more cake.
[Music]
Jessie didn't even ask me, she just
warning.
You probably misunderstood her.
No, he's taking care of the whole wedding.
This is getting worse.
Yes I know.
We must put a lock on the door
so that it doesn't come in. so that it doesn't come out.
What are you talking about?
Did you hear what I just said about
Jessie?
Yes. He wants to help and you should accept it.
Help. No, no. She wants to do everything alone.
She and her henchwoman are doing it no matter what.
Where are you going?
[Music]
Alexa,
What are you doing? It's late, everyone's asleep.
Did you move to my neighborhood?
Yes, I had to rent this house to be
close and plan the wedding of
No, you won't plan that wedding.
She's my daughter. I'll do this. I've dreamed of
this all my life.
You have two daughters and you will have your
opportunity. You'll get your chance.
This is my chance. You're the mother.
of the groom, not of the bride.
Did you understand? And you won't take my
opportunity? Did you hear?
Yes, I think the whole neighborhood loves you.
You heard right. Everything is clear.
And take that off. You look ridiculous.
Honey, what are you doing? It's 2 o'clock in the morning.
tomorrow.
I know. Just give me a few more minutes.
and I'll go to bed.
You must work very early.
No, I'll work at home tomorrow. I can
do both at the same time.
I like that wedding cake better.
000 for a wedding dress. Now that
the dresses cost.
We need to talk about the budget for the
wedding.
We're not going to discuss that at midnight.
When is a good time to
discuss it?
All right, honey. I'm going to bed.
Add the wedding cake to your designs.
[Music]
Please,
Run fast. I can see you. Hey,
here
We have to prepare ourselves. We are ready.
this way quickly.
Run here quickly.
I don't think so. Bot Taylor
looks shorter in person.
I think you know what you're doing.
The coach made us see all your
games.
All right. Give him some space.
Calm down, guys.
It's an honor to meet you. I've seen your
games since I was in high school.
I have followed your entire career, I have seen
all your games. Okay, okay,
keep practicing.
Don't get excited, I just wanted to see how it goes.
all.
It seems they have been training for a while.
Oh yeah, we're early.
97 is Jeremy, the team captain.
I think I could improve that a little bit.
move.
Oh really,
Why don't you stay and help us?
I just came to see, coach.
Okay, just seeing you.
[Music]
Oh, Ravin,
Good morning.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, you were awake.
Yes, there is a lot to do. I just
begin.
Mom, I think this is not
It's okay, I can do everything. You and your
Grandma is still my priority.
Okay, then Clara will see it.
later. Jessie has my wedding book
at home. We can watch it together.
Yes, I know what's best for you.
Besides, we don't need them. You and I
We'll do this together and I'll turn you into
the most beautiful bride of all.
I promise.
It's very cute, Mom, but I don't think it's
my style.
What nonsense. This is the best style.
I know, I'm a designer.
Me atoré.
The coach will not stop insisting.
Can you imagine? B. Taylor as coordinator
CARS offensive.
Yes. Well, let's talk under the tree. Yes.
Okay. I was in the field all day.
I'll see outside.
Ah, very well. This is the house.
Wow, she's beautiful.
And this is the kitchen. Only Clara enters.
You can't come into my house when you're
give it a win, Jessie.
Yes, I really must take action.
around the house.
In the garden. Imagine I'm not here.
This can't be true. I can't believe this.
Are those your ideas for the wedding,
Jessie, what are we literally talking about?
last night?
Do you want to plan a wedding?
Yeah,
but
We just have a few ideas to add to
yours, like
this tiara.
What do you think of these tiaras for the
bridesmaids?
They are horrible.
I bought you one too. Oh yeah. Mm.
Oh,
that makes you look so young.
Jessie, get this out of my head.
Now
[Music]
how we played in this tree with the
grandfather?
It was always so peaceful out here.
Maybe this was a mistake, having the wedding
at home.
I forgot how controlling she can be.
It's enough to come home and
return to the same thing.
It is a very small city.
Could you be happy as a coordinator?
offensive?
This is my big day. I don't decide about
nothing.
This is my life and I can't decide about it.
she.
He didn't even ask me what I wanted.
I don't know what I want.
I know what I want, but I don't think I'll
let him have it.
I got what I wanted.
We should have what we want.
You're talking about a silly wedding. I'm talking
of the rest of my life.
My wedding is not stupid, it is important for
my.
I'm sorry.
I thought you were here to listen to me.
It's because everything is always about
You. Why don't you do something for others?
and you teach those American kids?
I better go back and make sure they haven't
nothing else changed.
I think it looks great.
Hey,
enough is enough.
Stop fighting over my big day. No.
we need your help.
Mom, my mom.
Oh, the tiara.
Oh, it's mine.
It's okay. Oh, Mom, you really must
stop escaping.
Escape.
Ah.
W called me. He wants his lunch.
Mom is gone now. She died a long time ago.
Ven.
We're going to a party.
I don't think you should wear that hairstyle.
You must be hungry.
Maybe you should tie him up.
I will cook what you like.
How do you know I like it?
Let's take a look at our houses.
Imagine your life as a kingdom. What is it?
the current condition of your castle?
Who lives in your castle? Is there any
conflict? Who lives in the tower of the
Castle? Is anyone trapped there?
up? Is the bridge up or down?
It's overwhelming.
Oh, please. Are you serious? Could it be?
your castle with your eyes closed?
I'm an open book.
My castle is full.
Climb onto my bridge.
I think I need to lower my bridge. Okay.
He told us that my children should invite their
friends.
Mm. I'll literally shut down my kingdom.
There you see it. It's a dragon.
You named him Jessie.
It's Jessie.
Yeah.
Well, I don't want my friends to be
children tell their parents about the disaster
that it's my house. It's true.
Well, my husband wants us to move.
our castle to Florida.
What? It can't be.
Yes. And we are fighting because there is no
way to keep my children away from their
schools or their friends.
Oh, I'm so sorry. It's so hard.
Well, I think my castle is the
opposite to yours.
We took my daughter to college on
weekend and my castle was
empty, sad, lonely and very quiet.
Enjoy the quiet days.
You are welcome as a nanny in my
noisy castle. Whenever you want.
It's okay. No, no, no, no, no. It's something
useful. There it is.
my kingdom.
[Music]
Raven, what do you think?
This will look beautiful with your figure.
No, I want something simple and vintage.
Vintage simple.
I want to be different.
It's not bad to be different. Thank you,
Grandma. I think this is your style.
Yes, but that dress will accentuate your
hip.
Do you know what will look beautiful with your
figure? This dress.
No, Jessie, this.
How about this blue one? Ah,
No, Raven, blue is not your color.
I think I have a suggestion. Raiden,
Yeah,
come with me.
[Music]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. They are all
Citín, they are unique.
Better not touch anything. Yes, very well.
wanna.
[Music]
Oh, it can't be.
Oh,
she is not beautiful.
Oh yes.
Oh,
I've waited all my life for this
moment. Yes, it's beautiful, but it's something
big and not what I wanted.
But you look beautiful, darling.
You look like a princess.
Yes, you are my princess.
Ah, our princess.
No, my princess.
Where is your mom?
[Music]
You look perfect in this dress.
Oh my God. Mom, alcohol.
Me atoré.
No. Mom, that's enough. It's fair. It's fair.
[Music]
I want to keep shopping.
No, Mom, no more shopping today.
Alexa, don't worry, I'll turn off the
dress.
Mom, let's go.
Hello, honey. How are you?
Hi, Mom. Are you with Ravin?
Yes. Jessie, give me my phone.
Hello, my love. I miss you so much. When
will they let you back, love?
In fact, that's why I called you.
You'll have to sit down.
You know what? I won't actually make it.
[Music]
Cugar
10.
[Applause]
We are.
Prepare information. 35 44.
What coach? Play action is so
predictable.
You need to align them better than that. All of them
They saw it coming. Hey, you move. Go or
stay here. Well, someone must
lead this team.
[Applause]
[Music]
Jeremy,
[Applause]
[Music]
Cooker 7, Gets 10.
You'll run this way. You'll take care of
this one and you will block this one.
Got it? You can do it. You can.
do it. Yes. On the count of three. 1,
two, three.
That is.
[Music]
[Applause]
It's free. It's free. It's free. It's
has. Has it. Yes. Huga.
[Applause]
Yeah.
Wow. It feels good to win again.
Thanks, Bo.
They did it.
Yes, but it was under your direction.
So we made it.
It's good to have you back on the team,
son.
You know something, coach?
It's good to be back on the team.
Yes, yes.
I must congratulate them. They did a very good job.
work, especially you. Ah.
You did it.
Understand,
what's going on?
It's her dress.
They found the dress, honey, it is
incredible what I read in those magazines
that you gave me, that you thought I didn't read,
but I did it. They said this is the
most important part of every wedding and
You guys did it. I think this is
very exciting for You are upset.
Are you upset?
It's because our daughter is getting married. I know,
I know. I feel the same when But it is
Well, it's happening. But it's a new
step, is another step in another direction
in our lives. And yes, I think this
it's lovely.
That's not Raven's dress.
It's your dress.
Things are not as I planned.
Whose dress is that?
Oh no. I don't like this role.
I don't like this role. It's wrong.
written. They made a mistake. It's wrong
written. We must talk to them about
This. This is
Listen. You're looking at the new
Cugars offensive coordinator. Wow.
Don't worry, it's a good thing. I need it.
I have a purpose again.
Nathan was drafted.
We have six weeks to get married.
We are in W's office.
Mother,
This will be a lot of fun.
This place was recommended to me
and they play games. I think this morning
They play bingo. Do you like bingo?
Oh really?
Yeah.
I'll be back for you at 4 at the latest. It's
okay, mom.
No, I want to stay with you.
It will be fun.
I promise I won't bother you. I'll take care of myself.
fine. I can stay with
such. Welcome to Seasons. I tell you
something, it's your lucky day. It's Monday
Bingo. You must be Loreta Gomez.
Hello, I'm Geraldine. I'm happy that
be here.
Don't leave me. I won't cause trouble anymore.
I promise.
Please,
Alexa.
It's okay. You're going to have a lot of fun.
will amuse you so much that you won't want to.
Nobody
can take care of me like you.
Here we go. Good morning.
[Music]
Alexa,
I promise I'll be back, Mom.
You helped with Duboa's account. This
it will be a big change.
[Music]
Hello, I'm working. I can't.
talking on the phone. All good.
Yes, I'm fine. My first official game.
as a coach is Tuesday at 6 pm.
It's very important to me. Write it in
your calendar.
Yes, of course, I'll be there.
B7.
B.
I remember when I was seven.
Don't you?
N1.
N41.
Call my husband. It's clear that I'm
in the wrong place.
Okay. I'm sure it is. Let's see if
someone manages to get a bingo.
O7.
Someone won. Won what, O71.
We're having fun. Uh.
M36.
[Music]
calling season.
Alexa Taylor.
Yeah,
dear, your mother escaped.
That?
Do you know where he could have gone?
It's my mom.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I feel.
All right, everyone, let's reflect.
[Applause]
[Music]
Mom, mom,
Here I am. It's okay. Okay, calm down.
Everything's fine. Ah, nothing's wrong. Here
I'm.
[Music]
That was it
the worst experience of my life.
You're being a little dramatic, aren't you?
do you think?
How could you leave me in a place like
that?
It was just a one-time thing. I've been very busy.
and I can't leave you alone at home. Oh, what
nonsense. I'm a grown woman.
Leaving me alone at home, what nonsense.
And what has you so busy, Alexa? I
had no problem doing anything
thing when I was your age. What
you need is to learn to organize your
time.
I do the best I can.
Of course, darling.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Why do you feel that way?
I'm just
tired.
So many things have happened. There's B Raven
is getting married. I have a job, I'm just
tired. Who are you?
Who are you?
Let me out of the car.
Don't worry, we'll go home.
I need help.
John was right. I can't do everything.
No one can. Wonder Woman is just
a character in a movie.
I know, but I didn't want to miss anything. And
now I'm missing everything.
A typical case of FOMO.
FOMO
it's obvious.
What is FOMO?
The fear of missing out.
Exactly. That's how I've felt.
But I didn't know how to say it.
Wow. You learn something new every day. So
I sit all the time.
And how could it not be, with this thing in our
hands. You can't always be connected
and disconnected at the same time. It is
impossible.
And the worst of all this is that
we experience the fear of missing out
more. It means that we don't trust that
God put us where we should be.
That's true.
Okay. My name is Alexa Taylor and
I need help.
Hello, Alexa.
Hello.
Oh, that felt like a ton of
bricks that just fell from my
shoulders.
We'll take care of it. What do you need?
You are busy too.
You were the first one at my door when my
son fractured his leg.
Yes, but it was different.
What do we do with each other?
Very good.
Now I only have 5 weeks left
planning my daughter's wedding. My mom was
expelled from the center.
Very sorry.
Y spent500
of the budget
from my daughter's wedding and I thought that the
days of going to my son's games
had finished and now I must do it again
new. And I can't keep watching how
Jess interferes and saves the day.
I love your mother, she makes me laugh a lot.
I'll take Fridays.
That would be great.
Thank you. I also need help
Wednesday to go with Ravin to your list
of gifts.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you. Good.
I think I can do that.
Yeah.
Alexa, count me in.
Thank you, girls. Thank you.
Well, today we will see our project of
life and we will answer the question that
characterizes me. The Bible says that the
King Acabe did evil in the eyes of the
Lord more than those before him.
Do we have a chance to improve or
make things worse than our parents
did they do?
Great. Now I must accept that I am
just like my father. Ah, that's a bad thing.
Well, there's a reason why none
has met him. Here we have the
opportunity to see our past to
change the future. Go to page 29.
We will use the stones as reminders.
Think about important events in your life.
life and put them on the stones. I could
be something in your childhood, the death of a
father, a successful job or the
birth of a child.
What are you doing?
Now they will stick a bird in the area where
managed to prosper. Then add three
if it was a time of growth.
And we will use the stars to mark the
things that are still unresolved.
Yes, yes.
[Music]
Bo's injury
It's a big stone that I haven't worked with.
had time to deal.
And my father's death is a stone
noticeable that I can't get rid of because my
Mom constantly talks about him as if
were still alive.
And to the one Raven didn't tell me about
Nathan.
That's what hurts me the most.
I really don't want to carry the stone.
to be like my father.
Wouldn't it be nice if we didn't have to anymore?
carry all that.
All right, everyone listen. Show them the
new move, Bo.
Okay, here's what we'll do.
Roby, you'll throw it to Kevin. Here,
Tyler, you'll run around. Block the
right. Left, right. Wait,
We've never made that move. This is what
what I thought.
Do you really want to win the championship?
No offense, Bot Taylor, but I know
to this team better than you.
And I know American better than you.
Intent only.
And you have played professionally,
I am the captain of this team
and I am the coach of this team.
Okay, okay, calm down,
Jeremy.
We'll make Bo's move. It's his decision.
The rest of you can go now.
Can you believe you are questioning me,
Bob?
Leadership is just more than just
order.
We are the coaches, we know what it is
better. I didn't order them when they won
the championship. I listened to his ideas.
Yes, I was right then and I am right.
now.
We teach kids to be leaders.
It is our true purpose. It is not
about who is right.
It's about winning, Coach. I know how.
gain.
Yes, that's true.
But what do you gain when you lose your
trust?
I've already lost everything. I don't care about his
confidence. To be a leader you need your
Confidence. Jeremy is right. Train him.
according to their abilities.
Believe me, they need new plays.
No, you need more experience.
What am I doing here?
He's an American high school student. Who
does it matter to you?
You know what matters? A million people.
seeing you.
I don't care about these players
beginners or this small town in
middle of nowhere. I managed to do something
and I don't want to be a conformist like you,
coach.
Wow.
If you keep living in the past,
you will never have a future.
Why don't you stop being nice to me and
let me go?
GOOD,
wherever you go, I hope that
find what you're looking for. See you.
Yes, it smells very good.
I think this will help.
No problem. Leave it to God. This
it's very hot.
[Music]
We are going to gain stature.
[Applause]
[Music]
Raquel has experienced the love of her
wife.
Thank you so much.
She and Jose were offered more
protection if they traveled to the house that
They promised. They also have more time
to be together.
This also helps them a lot.
Tasting Monday.
Oh, this takes a long time.
It's ready. I think we're done. Here
good
you tour and tour.
Are you eating? You can't.
And you, please. Let's finish.
Hey, be careful.
[Music]
Did you do this?
No, I think it was him.
Oh really,
It means we have the night to
us. Enjoy time with your
husband.
You must take your medicine.
No, get that away from my face. The more
Take it quickly, I can do it sooner
make your breakfast.
Mom, it's time to go.
Mother.
[Music]
Mom, why aren't you ready?
I don't have anything scheduled for Tuesday.
Mom, it's Monday. We have a date for
the gifts and the menu test in the
tasting.
I thought that was Wednesday.
I don't have anyone to help me today. Alexa, it's
Well, these things happen.
I'll take care of Fredy.
No,
Just give me two seconds, now.
I'm coming back. Don't leave.
Hurry up.
[Applause]
All right, everyone listen up.
I just want to tell you something. You practiced and
They worked hard for this and this is what they live for.
Today is the day. Leave everything there.
Did you understand? I don't want anything here. Leave
all your effort there. Are you ready?
Let's play now. Now. Now.
Jeremy. Jeremy, it's time. You
You can. That's it. Let's go. Line up.
Okay, coach.
[Music]
[Applause]
Hi, are you from the Taylor wedding?
Yes, miss. We
here.
Mother,
don't you dare touch the cakes.
This table is Italian cuisine. Here it is
the Asian infusion and here the party
Mexican. You can try whatever you like.
Ah, no, no, sorry, but the party
Mexican is not appropriate for this wedding.
Where is the French cuisine?
I don't have French cuisine on the list,
but we could improvise.
In fact, I think Mexican food is
Perfect for a garden wedding, isn't it?
do you believe?
Seriously, Alexa, seriously. Because no
We only serve hot dogs and hamburgers in
a grill and we have a wedding type
grill.
All right, let's make it a barbecue.
We have the cake tests over here.
Heard.
[Applause]
Let's go to the court.
I wanted Italian food,
But Raven, French cuisine is more
elegant. Ah, I agree, but my
Mom, if you bring me the best lasagna
memories of my childhood and I would love to
something like that at my wedding.
I'm glad you like my lasagna. I could
make it for the wedding if you want.
Yes, no, actually we won't be giving food.
landlady at my son's wedding.
I can make one for you. Thanks. Ah,
Where is Loreta?
Mother.
Loretta,
mother.
[Applause]
28.
Go check it out, go with him. Follow the
play. Come on, focus on the game.
All right, that's all. Sit down, sit down.
[Music]
What happened to me?
You got hit hard. No one saw it coming.
Hey, hey, calm down, take it easy.
It's bad.
I don't know, but the nurse will come and we
will say that he has. Yes,
Jeremy, listen.
I'm sorry.
I feel like everything is my fault.
I pushed you too hard.
The team can't win without me.
They definitely can't win without you
leadership.
Jeremy Lin,
My name is Cindy World, I am an assistant of
surgery. I work with Dr. Hawking.
I'm here to explain it to you.
knee.
That's good news. It's a sprain.
You will be on bed rest for at least two weeks.
on crutches. Okay? You must keep
the knee stretched, elevated with ice and
I assume you're the coach. Work
With your coach, your will be rehabilitated
knee, then you will have a check-up
with the doctor. Okay. Do you have any
Question? Very well, thank you.
I'm not going to sit on the sidelines and watch how
everyone plays without me.
Jeremy,
listen to me.
In high school
I went through something similar.
I had to rest a couple of games.
It was difficult.
I wanted to quit,
but the coach didn't let me. I still haven't
already.
No matter how difficult it is, you
you will recover
and you will return to the countryside.
Remember,
you are part of this team.
Thanks, coach.
I have to go. I'll see you soon. Yes, of
agreement.
What's going on? Come on.
Grandma fell.
That?
Alright.
I don't know, but take this. Help me a bit.
moment, please. Good. He had a serious
brain trauma from his fall. His
skull was fractured and hemorrhaged
in the brain. We couldn't stop the
bleeding. We couldn't save her.
I feel.
[Music]
Calm down, honey. Calm down.
I have for you.
Youve been walking through.
[Music]
I see your troubles
breaking you.
You're looking for something
you still haven found.
Take
I have
[Music]
come and rest
here inside my love.
[Music]
Now it seems silly.
Long have I waited
for your eyes to see
my love is here
all to make you new.
[Music]
Open your heart to this love I have for
you.
[Music]
In my heart
love burns like a
for you my beloved my desire.
[Music]
Alexa,
how's everything going?
Thank you for the flowers.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
You have the designs ready for Duba,
because yesterday was the I didn't have time.
This isn't working. Even when
you are here you are not here.
I hate to do this, Alexa, but I'll have to.
let you go.
Thank you.
[Music]
Contact me with Christopher Duboa.
Maybe it was for the best.
I've never been fired.
I didn't mean that. They're happening.
many things.
We need to plan a funeral. I'm not
ready to deal with it.
We have to do it.
No, we are planning a wedding now.
Okay. I'll take care of the funeral.
Stop saying funeral.
I heard.
Stop saying okay.
And what do you want me to say?
It's not just happening to you,
I also took care of your mother for a long time
time. My daughter will also get married and
I have a job. I have supported you and I have not
said nothing about it.
I feel like I've been supporting you all my life.
[Music]
Listen, I like to help you,
but I need the same from you.
I lost her too.
I would have liked to say goodbye to her.
You go.
[Music]
It's not a good time, Jessie.
I'm really sorry for your loss,
Alexa.
I stayed up all night
thinking about this. I wish I had put
attention.
I feel responsible.
What's so funny? How can you be?
able to turn my mother's death
in something of yours? Alexa,
Hey, Nathan and I talked all night.
night. We decided to take the pressure off them and
escape.
That?
Of course not.
Of course they won't run away.
We're in this together.
No, my only son.
No, my only daughter. This is my decision.
I know my son would never agree.
with this.
This is our decision.
Listen, listen. Call Clara.
Conover, what's your name? Can you
call her?
We will have a wedding in my garden in a
month, okay? I won't lose this.
also.
[Music]
Clara, yes,
I can't take this anymore. Nobody listens to me.
I want. I want to run away.
What? Raiden drove all night for
begin my bridesmaid duties.
I know. Don't worry, my mother won't let me.
Neither does my future mother-in-law. I've had to
discard every idea of my wedding since
I arrived. They are so controlling, the only thing
All they do is fight. They never stop fighting.
and nobody asks me what I want.
Raven, what do you want?
I have no idea anymore.
That's what we're here for.
I know. I wish my mother would
would ask.
I understand, but you already told him.
I just want her to be happy.
sacrificing your happiness at your wedding.
Raven, it's okay to want what you want.
I'm sure that deep down your mother
wants you to be happy, but can't
make you happy if you don't tell him that
want.
It's true, I can imagine everything.
We can put lights on these trees.
Do you want to run away? Because if so,
then do it.
You know I don't want to do it.
That's what I thought.
Ah, the chairs for the ceremony can
go there and the bow can go there.
Does that sound okay to you, Rivin?
Yes, indeed, yes.
We'll put the reception and the track there.
Why is no one recording this?
Jessie, take out your phone. We have to go up.
this to the networks.
You know what I wish? I wish I had
the time to cut down that tree.
I can work with what I have.
Now guide me to your kitchen for
find out where the food will be.
B told me you were here. I'm so sorry.
your loss.
Oh, thanks. You're a great neighbor.
Who died?
My mother.
I'm so sorry. It looked good in the
engagement party.
Mom, we should do the wedding and the
funeral together.
That?
I think we should discuss this. No
There's nothing to discuss. Ah, well,
we should talk about this.
I don't want to honor my grandmother's life in
my wedding.
I could give you some ideas for that.
Seriously, honey,
Are you sure this is what
want?
I think it should be here. I know it.
also.
And that's what she was like. Yes, darling.
Now I can say something.
No,
I love you. I love you.
[Music]
Please, just one last time like the
Taylor family. It's just that it's Cursy, but
I want Yes, I just want one thing, just one
hug. A big hug.
I love you all.
I like being a Taylor.
I will miss you, daughter.
I'll miss being a Taylor.
I will miss you.
[Music]
Sorry to ruin this, but I have to go with
Excuse me.
Carefully.
I love you. We love you.
We love you.
[Music]
[Applause]
It just can't be.
What happened? It was supposed to fall from the other side.
side.
You never said that, ma'am. It should have been more
specific.
Why would I want it to fall here?
what would you want to cut it? I wanted to help
your mom cutting down trees. Jessie, do you
did you go crazy?
Because?
Why would you do something like that without consulting him?
with me?
You wanted to surprise yourself.
Wow, you didn't surprise me.
It's worth uploading to Instagram.
It was very important to me
and now it's ruined. I'm sorry.
I'll call Nathan. No.
Ah, you
I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
I ruined everything.
Let's not be so dramatic.
Ah, Alexa, I know I can be dramatic,
but I think this qualifies as drama.
I destroyed something that was important to me.
Raven. Yes,
maybe it's the worst thing that could have happened
past.
Nathan is going to kill me
and Paul is going to kill me. You would kill me
first. Jessie was being
Sarcastic. It's all good, it's just a
bow.
Thank God no one was hurt, no one
died.
Maybe so. Who?
Nathan
was recruited.
With
I can't go with him.
I can't keep him safe anymore.
I'm so sorry, Jessie.
I am very proud that my future
son-in-law serve our country.
I never wanted him to join the Navy.
I want him home with me.
Of course.
But now he's creating a new home.
I'm not ready to accept it yet.
I think we are never ready.
Nobody gave us a manual on how to
educate our children or they gave us
instructions on how to let them go.
I don't have to let go.
If I'm busy planning a wedding.
Exactly. And if you keep busy,
you will waste the time you have with him
now.
You're right. And I had to cut that
stupid tree.
Alexa,
I'm the queen of escape. I know that.
I'm sorry for the way I treated you. When our
children entered high school,
I was a horrible friend.
I was jealous of you because you were
strong and you had the courage to do it
correct. Now I've just pretended that nothing
It happened, but
In fact
I wanted us to be friends again.
As?
Stealing my time with my daughter.
That
is what you think he did?
Yes, that's exactly what you were doing.
No,
I was trying to prove that I could be a
good friend of the new one paying everything.
Well no, but by helping Raven he tried
help you.
Oh my God. I really made a mess of it.
all this.
Alexa, I'm so sorry about everything.
[Music]
You were right, darling.
That dress is perfect for you.
Thanks, Mom.
I thought I was being a better mother
of what my mother was to me
and apparently he was just following his
steps. mom,
I'm still mad at myself for your fear of
tell me who you would marry.
I never want you to be afraid to tell me
nothing. Yes,
I know. I'm sorry I didn't tell you about
Nathan.
I really didn't want it to be like this.
Listen,
[Music]
if the relationship between mother and daughter is
difficult, marriage is even worse.
But it's also beautiful.
And when it's hard, I want you to
feel free to talk to me about
yes indeed,
I know, I know. I need to start a new one.
stage in my life saying exactly what
I think.
Yes, always be honest with Nathan,
even about the small things, because
will stay that way.
AND
I spoke to Nathan and we both agreed that
you should have the wedding ring of the
Grandma if you want.
Mom, I thought it was a tradition.
familiar that you will use it now that it is
was.
Yes. Well, we'll break our patterns.
family one stone at a time.
Thank you, Mom. I'd be honored. Now
you have something old.
I love you.
[Music]
Pass.
You look beautiful.
[Music]
I brought you something blue. Thanks.
Can
join?
Yes, sure.
Raven,
I wanted to lend you this.
It belonged to Nathan's grandmother.
She used it when she got married. I used it when I
I got married. And now you will use it as
tradition.
Thanks, Jessie.
And now you'll be using something borrowed. I'll see you.
outside.
GOOD,
I'll see you outside.
And are you ready? Are you ready?
Who's ready for this moment?
[Music]
And it's never broken yet.
No matter how it's stretch
waking my soul to the beat of your
heart.
[Music]
I love you very much.
Who delivers this woman to be
married? her mother and I.
[Music]
It reminds me of when we got married.
We have gathered before you today and
before God
to witness Raven Taylor and
Nathan Adams. But before we begin
We would like to honor Loreta's life
Gomez.
Who has the urn?
Ravin, who has the urn?
Do you have it?
No.
Hey, here it is.
I got it, I got it.
I have it. Oh, I have it. Oh, I don't have it.
Thank you.
[Music]
He's already in heaven. We'll meet again.
ready.
[Music]
[Applause]
It's about time.
Let's go.
[Applause]
[Music]
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Nathan, can you kiss the bride?
[Applause]
[Music]
Let's go.
We did it
and I have no idea how.
Thanks to Clara Conover. That's how it was.
Alexa, you have a great style for it.
design.
Thank you.
I should be an interior designer.
You can join the team whenever you want.
Oh really?
Sorry.
What was that? I think I've got it now.
so it seems.
What do you think, Bob?
Ready for the next step?
I'm not getting married anytime soon, Coach.
one thing at a time.
I was talking about football.
You must have heard about my offer.
I was talking about the next season.
What are you talking about? I was waiting for the moment.
appropriate to tell him, "Do it
not at my sister's wedding." Hey, now
you must tell me.
I was offered to be offensive coordinator
with the possibility of being a coach in
boss.
Hey, that's great.
It doesn't feel like an obstacle. Yes,
of course not,
but I won't accept it.
Bo, as much as I like having you
fence,
you should think about it very carefully.
You're right. Training teenagers is not
is so attractive and it's not like being
coach at the university of time
complete. Well, I don't know.
A wise old man told me long ago,
"It's not success that matters, but
those who are by your side.
Hey, be careful who you call old.
Hold on a second.
Would you help us with the program in
instead of being a coach in the
university?
I would say the adventure continues.
Hello, how are you?
We are doing very well.
Okay, perfect.
Why don't parents travel after
of the wedding? Do we do it all?
Yes. It should be our gift.
Yeah.
We paid for the entire wedding.
Yes. What do we gain?
Grandchildren.
Don't get excited. We're too young to
being grandparents.
Calm down, they must be together for
give us grandchildren.
Congratulations, children.
[Applause]
Imagine Raiden alone in that huge
house. So she decided to stay with
us until Nathan returns. They have
lucky to stay with his daughter for a little while
further.
Well, don't worry, Christmas is coming.
And John and I would like your
family will visit us on vacation.
Oh really.
Oh, I'm so happy we're friends.
again.
Yes, they won't have to wait that long.
What? We'll buy the house next door.
[Music]
The road kings of our kingdom.